(Bernadette:)Let's think.
Are we doing just Disney
or California Adventure too?
(Leonard:)It's nice of your old school to let us try out
our science talk on some female students.
They were actually pretty excited.
I'm their most famous alum.
(Howard:)If you don't count the serial killer
who ate all those prostitutes.
This must feel good for you, coming
back to your alma mater as an astronaut.
(Howard:)Yeah. Last time I was here
I was just a scrawny little nerd.
(Leonard:)And now you're also an astronaut.
(Howard:)So many memories.
How many times in these hallways...
...was I tripped, punched and spit on? Heh.
(Howard:)Oh, look, here's my old locker.
(Howard:)I have a masters in engineering...
(Howard:)...I still can't figure out how Scott Kapinski
got me and my briefcase to fit in there.